pureprofile.com 2019-10-03

# Privacy Policy - Pureprofile

## Info for personal accounts

Pureprofile is founded on the principle of making your everyday online activities more valuable. We know that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously.

By visiting and using Pureprofile, you are accepting the practices outlined in this policy.

By registering a personal account, you’ll be asked to provide some personal and sensitive information, as detailed here and in our Terms of Service.

Our Privacy Policy is based on the following provisions:

  * You can request to update or change profile information at any time
  * You can opt-out of Pureprofile and close your account at any time
  * We only store profile information you choose to provide. We use the latest technologies and best practises to protect all personal information from unauthorised physical and electronic access and interference
  * We don’t permit businesses to access your personal information, unless you decide to make this information available
  * We don’t forward or transfer your information to any third parties, other than the organisations detailed in this document, which are required to operate Pureprofile. This disclosure is necessary in your Pureprofile use and these organisations are required to respect and maintain our commitments to your privacy and security

We are absolutely committed to these policies. If you have any concerns or questions relating to this document or our Terms of Service, please feel free to contact us

Pureprofile is founded on the principle of making the things you do online more valuable. We know that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and as a result, we take your privacy very seriously. By registering a personal account, you agree to understand and accept this Privacy Policy.

### What information do we collect?

We collect three broad types of information:

  * Information you directly provide us;
  * Information about your use and interaction with Pureprofile; and
  * Information collected through the platform, applications, third parties or other websites

  1. Information you directly provide us can include:

  * the email address and password you provide when registering an account;
  * profile information;
  * any responses you submit during activities;
  * the content of any customer service correspondence;
  * your login details for other associated apps you’ve registered with;
  * any banking details you provide when requesting a redemption; or
  * any other information you directly provide on Pureprofile 

  2. Information about your use and interaction with Pureprofile can include:

  * your IP address, geolocation and data stored in Pureprofile cookies;
  * your activities on Pureprofile, such as when you accept or skip an invitation, your participation in activities and your progression through a particular activity;
  * your other account activity, such as when you login to your account, when you send us customer service correspondence and when you opt-in to an application;
  * information about the device you’re using to access Pureprofile; or
  * your transaction history, including your account balance, the payments you receive from participating in activities and any rewards you have requested 

  3. Information collected through the platform, applications, third parties or other websites can include:

  * details about yourself, which are stored on other websites;
  * the names, email addresses and other details of contacts or friends you have stored on other websites; and
  * any other data that may be stored on other websites or held by third parties

We collect three types of information. The information you give us, the information about your online interactions and information we gather via third parties.

### How do we use the information we collect?

**Pureprofile’s use of information**

We use the information you provide us to publish and deliver insights and relevant activities to you through Pureprofile. This can include:

  * Sending you emails or notifications to alert you of activities for which you may qualify (if you have opted in to receiving such notifications);
  * Using responses from an activity, which has been provided to a business in a de-identified way, for further analysis or use, including publication of the de-identified results;
  * Help detect and prevent fraudulent activity;
  * Maintain the data quality of activity responses;
  * Improve and personalise your Pureprofile experience;
  * Maintain, operate and improve Pureprofile; and
  * Promote our services on affiliated third party websites using banner ads or other materials

 **Businesses’ use of information**

There are times when businesses may require access to profile information such as:

  * Profile information to help determine the target audience for an activity; or
  * The responses you submit during an activity

All information provided to businesses will be presented in an aggregated and de-identified format, unless you grant us express permission to do otherwise.

Businesses are also allowed to ask you to provide your name, email address and other contact information during an activity. You should know that:

  * you are providing this information directly to the business and not Pureprofile;
  * your information will be dealt with in accordance with the relevant business’ Privacy Policy and not Pureprofile’s Privacy Policy; and
  * you are always free to decline providing contact details to a business

 **Targeted advertising**

We may use the information we collect (for example, email address and Pureprofile cookies) to send you targeted advertising on third party sites. The purpose of this retargeted advertising could be to provide you with a relevant experience through a third party site or to encourage you to login to your account.

Your information helps to match and deliver relevant activities to you through Pureprofile. Sometimes it’ll be used directly by us and sometimes by our partners. Either way, your data will always be protected and de-identified.

Information collected through the platform, applications, third parties and other websites may be used by you to allow you to:

Create a relationship between your account and other online accounts you’ve registered for;

  * invite your friends to join Pureprofile;
  * communicate with your friends and contacts about Pureprofile;
  * view and access your online accounts through the site;
  * complete some of your profile information using information stored on another website;
  * help detect and prevent fraudulent activity;
  * improve the accessibility of the site; and
  * participate in retargeting activities

When you use Pureprofile, you can use the information you collect for a variety of activities like connecting your social media accounts, telling your friends about Pureprofile or get in touch with us to report a bug or ask suggest improvements to the site.

### Accessing and controlling your information

If you:

  * want to obtain access to any personal information that we hold about you;
  * object to profiling, including profiling for marketing purposes;
  * believe any of your personal information that we hold is inaccurate, incomplete or it is not necessary to hold it; or
  * want to delete your personal information from our records,

you can contact us using one of the channels listed in the ‘Contact Us’ section. We will use reasonable efforts to resolve your request within 30 days.

We will provide you with our reasons if we refuse your request and, if you disagree, you are entitled to ask us to make a note of the request with your information.

You may also request that your personal information be restricted from processing where one of the following applies:

  * we are verifying the accuracy of personal information , which you believe to be inaccurate;
  * the processing is unlawful and you oppose the erasure of personal information;
  * we no longer require the personal information but you require it for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; and
  * you have objected to processing and we are verifying whether there are legitimate grounds to refuse the objection

You’re in control. Access, update, change and delete your Pureprofile information whenever you need to.

### Disclosure to third parties

We will not sell, trade, give or rent any information to a third party unless:

  1. you have expressly consented;
  2. such disclosure is permitted by the Terms of Service or this Privacy Policy; or
  3. required to do so by law

When we provide information to third parties, profile information and activity responses are only disclosed to businesses in an aggregate and de-identified format. We never provide any personally identifiable Information about you to a business, unless you expressly grant us permission to do so. This permission will (unless otherwise indicated) generally be required on a case-by-case basis.

 **Banking details**

We only disclose your banking details to our bank for the purpose of actioning your reward requests. This disclosure occurs in an extremely secure and protected online facility.

 **Overseas staff handling your data**

The response data for some activities may be stored and/or analysed and aggregated by staff residing in the United States, United Kingdom, Australia, Greece and India. Our staff, including contractors, are required to maintain the same privacy and data protection standards as required under the General Data Protection Regulation.

 **Overseas third parties**

Some activities may originate from businesses based outside of your country of residence and accordingly, you agree to allow your activity response data to be provided to these businesses. When this happens, we may need to use third party hosting facilities located outside of your country of residence to ensure your information is constantly accessible and backed up in secure data storage facilities. We will ensure all third party hosting providers used are not permitted access to your information.

 **Data matching**

We may share your information with third parties to determine if these parties already hold information about you. We do this for the following purposes:

  * to seek your consent to add the information held by third parties to your Pureprofile account; and
  * to determine if you qualify for an activity (for example for businesses who want to deploy a survey to individuals already on their database)

If the third party does not hold information about you, we ensure that the information we shared with them is destroyed.

 **Linking to other websites**

If you associate your account with another website or online account through a Pureprofile product, we may save any data retrieved via this association into our system. In this case, the nature of the data being transferred will be outlined to you and require your express consent. Read the terms of any application carefully before accepting and using an application.

We’ll protect your information from all third parties, other than the specified organisations necessary for running of Pureprofile.

We are committed to providing a secure online environment to use Pureprofile and have invested considerable resources to protect your information from loss, misuse, corruption and unauthorised access. More precisely, we have invested in:

  * A secure server software (SSL) technology to encrypt the transfer of all personally identifiable information
  * Firewalls that protect against unauthorised access of all of the data we collect and store

Due to the nature of the internet, it’s possible that information stored on our servers and data transmitted online can sometimes be accessed by unauthorised third parties. While we make significant investments to ensure that this risk is minimised, we cannot guarantee the information you provided us will never be compromised. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you acknowledge and accept these risks.

We’re doing everything we can to provide a safe environment for you. This means we’re staying up-to-date with fancy technology and fighting crazy hackers. However, we can’t promise it’ll be perfect and can’t guarantee a risk-free experience.

### Closing your Pureprofile account

Using Pureprofile and maintaining an account is completely opt-in and you may close your Pureprofile account at any time. You’re always able to dissociate your account from any application or website you’ve previously linked to your personal account. Upon dissociating your account, we’ll provide you the option of having all associated data deleted from our records.

We’ll be sad to see you go, but if you want to close your account and retrieve all recorded data, you’re always able to.

If you have any enquiries or complaints about either our Privacy Policies or procedures, including requesting access to or correcting personal information that Pureprofile holds, please get in touch via the Contact Us section of our site, with the subject heading “Attention: Privacy Officer”.

Contact us if you have questions or complaints related to our Privacy Policy.

We may make changes to the Privacy Policy from time to time and you’ll be notified of any changes.

Ch-ch-ch-ch-changes! We’ll let you know when these happen.
